<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lambda Tools on Docs</title><link>/user-guide/lambda-tools/</link><description>Recent content in Lambda Tools on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/user-guide/lambda-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hot Reloading</title><link>/user-guide/lambda-tools/hot-reloading/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/lambda-tools/hot-reloading/</guid><description>Hot reloading (formerly known as hot swapping) continuously applies code changes to Lambda functions without manual redeployment.
Quickly iterating over Lambda function code can be quite cumbersome, as you need to deploy your function on every change. LocalStack enables fast feedback cycles during development by automatically reloading your function code. Pro users can also hot-reload Lambda layers.
Note The magic S3 bucket name changed from __local__ to hot-reload in LocalStack v2.</description></item><item><title>Remote Debugging</title><link>/user-guide/lambda-tools/debugging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/lambda-tools/debugging/</guid><description>Overview This guide covers remote debugging of Lambda functions with the IDEs Visual Studio Code and IntelliJ IDEA. For a simple working example of this feature, check out Pro sample lambda-mounting-and-debugging.
More examples and tooling support for local Lambda debugging (including support for other IDEs like PyCharm) is coming soon - stay tuned!
Covered Topics Debugging Python lambdas Debugging JVM lambdas Debugging Node.js lambdas Useful Links Debugging Python lambdas Lambda functions debugging used to be a difficult task.</description></item><item><title>VSCode Extension</title><link>/user-guide/lambda-tools/vscode-extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/lambda-tools/vscode-extension/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack VSCode Extension supports deploying and invoking Python Lambda functions through AWS SAM or AWS CloudFormation.
Prerequisites VS Code samlocal command line wrapper around the AWS SAM CLI for use with LocalStack. LocalStack running in the background. Getting Started You can use a sample project to get started with the extension. The sample project contains a simple Lambda function and a SAM template. Clone the repository and open the project in VSCode.</description></item></channel></rss>