<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free on Docs</title><link>/tags/free/</link><description>Recent content in Free on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/free/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>API Gateway</title><link>/user-guide/aws/apigateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/apigateway/</guid><description>Introduction API Gateway is a managed service that enables developers to create, deploy, and manage APIs (Application Programming Interfaces). It allows easy creation of REST, HTTP, and WebSocket APIs to securely access data, business logic, or functionality from backend services like AWS Lambda functions or EC2 instances. API Gateway supports standard HTTP methods such as GET, POST, PUT, PATCH, and DELETE and integrates with various AWS services, including Lambda, Cognito, CloudWatch, and X-Ray.</description></item><item><title>Certificate Manager (ACM)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/acm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/acm/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) is a service that enables you to create and manage SSL/TLS certificates that can be used to secure your applications and resources in AWS. You can use ACM to provision and deploy public or private certificates trusted by browsers and other clients.
ACM supports securing multiple domain names and subdomains and can create wildcard SSL certificates to protect an entire domain and its subdomains. You can also use ACM to import certificates from third-party certificate authorities or to generate private certificates for internal use.</description></item><item><title>CloudFormation</title><link>/user-guide/aws/cloudformation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/cloudformation/</guid><description>Introduction CloudFormation is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that allows you to define and provision infrastructure as code. It enables you to create, update, and manage resources in a repeatable and automated manner using declarative templates. With CloudFormation, you can use JSON or YAML templates to define your desired infrastructure state. You can specify resources, their configurations, dependencies, and relationships in these templates.
LocalStack supports CloudFormation, allowing you to use the CloudFormation APIs in your local environment to declaratively define your architecture on the AWS, including resources such as S3 Buckets, Lambda Functions, and much more.</description></item><item><title>CloudWatch</title><link>/user-guide/aws/cloudwatch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/cloudwatch/</guid><description>CloudWatch is a comprehensive monitoring and observability service that Amazon Web Services (AWS) provides. It allows you to collect and track metrics, collect and monitor log files, and set alarms. CloudWatch provides valuable insights into your AWS resources, applications, and services, enabling you to troubleshoot issues, optimize performance, and make informed decisions.
LocalStack allows you to use CloudWatch APIs on your local machine to create and manage CloudWatch resources, such as custom metrics, alarms, and log groups, for local development and testing purposes.</description></item><item><title>CloudWatch Logs</title><link>/user-guide/aws/logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/logs/</guid><description>CloudWatch Logs allows to store and retrieve logs. While some services automatically create and write logs (e.g. Lambda), logs can also be added manually. CloudWatch Logs is available in the Community version. However, some specific features are only available in Pro.
Subscription Filters Subscription filters can be used to forward logs to certain services, e.g. Kinesis, Lambda, and Kinesis Data Firehose. You can read upon details in the official AWS docs.</description></item><item><title>Config</title><link>/user-guide/aws/config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/config/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Config is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to assess, audit, and manage the configuration state of your AWS resources. Config provides a comprehensive view of the resource configuration across your AWS environment, helping you ensure compliance with security policies, track changes, and troubleshoot operational issues. Config continuously records configuration changes and allows you to retain a historical record of these changes.
LocalStack allows you to use the Config APIs in your local environment to assesses resource configurations and notifies you of any non-compliant items to mitigate potential security risks.</description></item><item><title>Data Firehose</title><link>/user-guide/aws/firehose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/firehose/</guid><description>Note This service was formerly called as &amp;lsquo;Kinesis Data Firehose&amp;rsquo;. Introduction Data Firehose is a service provided by AWS that allows you to extract, transform and load streaming data into various destinations, such as Amazon S3, Amazon Redshift, and Elasticsearch. With Data Firehose, you can ingest and deliver real-time data from different sources as it automates data delivery, handles buffering and compression, and scales according to the data volume.</description></item><item><title>DynamoDB</title><link>/user-guide/aws/dynamodb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/dynamodb/</guid><description>DynamoDB is a fully managed NoSQL database service provided by AWS. It offers a flexible and highly scalable way to store and retrieve data, making it suitable for a wide range of applications. DynamoDB provides a fast and scalable key-value datastore with support for replication, automatic scaling, data encryption at rest, and on-demand backup, among other capabilities.
LocalStack allows you to use the DynamoDB APIs in your local environment to manage key-value and document data models.</description></item><item><title>Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/ec2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/ec2/</guid><description>Introduction Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) is a core service within Amazon Web Services (AWS) that provides scalable and flexible virtual computing resources. EC2 enables users to launch and manage virtual machines, referred to as instances.
LocalStack allows you to use the EC2 APIs in your local environment to create and manage EC2 instances and related resources such as VPCs, EBS volumes, etc. The list of supported APIs can be found on the API coverage page.</description></item><item><title>Elasticsearch Service</title><link>/user-guide/aws/es/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/es/</guid><description>The Elasticsearch Service in LocalStack lets you create one or more single-node Elasticsearch/OpenSearch cluster that behaves like the Amazon Elasticsearch Service. This service is, like its AWS counterpart, heavily linked with the OpenSearch Service. Any cluster created with the Elasticsearch Service will show up in the OpenSearch Service and vice versa.
Creating an Elasticsearch cluster You can go ahead and use awslocal to create a new elasticsearch domain via the aws es create-elasticsearch-domain command.</description></item><item><title>EventBridge</title><link>/user-guide/aws/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/events/</guid><description>Introduction EventBridge provides a centralized mechanism to discover and communicate events across various AWS services and applications. EventBridge allows you to register, track, and resolve events, which indicates a change in the environment and then applies a rule to route the event to a target. EventBridge rules are tied to an Event Bus to manage event-driven workflows. You can use either identity-based or resource-based policies to control access to EventBridge resources, where the former can be attached to IAM users, groups, and roles, and the latter can be attached to specific AWS resources.</description></item><item><title>EventBridge Pipes</title><link>/user-guide/aws/pipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/pipes/</guid><description>Introduction EventBridge Pipes allows users to create point-to-point integrations between event producers and consumers with transform, filter and enrichment steps. Pipes are particularly useful for scenarios involving real-time data processing, application integration, and automated workflows, while simplifying the process of routing events between AWS services. Pipes offer a point-to-point connection from one source to one target (one-to-one). In contrast, EventBridge Event Bus offers a one-to-many integration where an event router delivers one event to zero or more destinations.</description></item><item><title>EventBridge Scheduler</title><link>/user-guide/aws/scheduler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/scheduler/</guid><description>Introduction EventBridge Scheduler is a service that enables you to schedule the execution of your AWS Lambda functions, Amazon ECS tasks, and Amazon Batch jobs. You can use EventBridge Scheduler to create schedules that run at a specific time or at regular intervals. You can also use EventBridge Scheduler to create schedules that run within a flexible time window.
LocalStack allows you to use the Scheduler APIs in your local environment to create and run schedules.</description></item><item><title>Identity and Access Management (IAM)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/iam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/iam/</guid><description>Introduction Identity and Access Management (IAM) is a web service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables users to control access to AWS resources securely. IAM allows organizations to create and manage AWS users, groups, and roles, defining granular permissions to access specific AWS services and resources. By centralizing access control, administrators can enforce the principle of least privilege, ensuring users have only the necessary permissions for their tasks.</description></item><item><title>Key Management Service (KMS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/kms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/kms/</guid><description>Introduction Key Management Service (KMS) is a managed service that allows users to handle encryption keys within the Amazon Web Services ecosystem. KMS allows users to create, control, and utilize keys to encrypt and decrypt data, as well as to sign and verify messages. KMS allows you to create, delete, list, and update aliases, friendly names for your KMS keys, and tag them for identification and automation. You can check the official AWS documentation to understand the basic terms and concepts used in the KMS.</description></item><item><title>Kinesis Data Streams</title><link>/user-guide/aws/kinesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/kinesis/</guid><description>Introduction Kinesis Data Streams is an AWS service for ingesting, buffering, and processing data in high throughput data streams. It is used for applications that require real-time processing and deriving insights from data streams such as logs, metrics, user interactions, and sensor readings.
LocalStack allows you to use the Kinesis Data Streams APIs in your local environment from setting up data streams and configuring data processing to building real-time applications. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page.</description></item><item><title>Lambda</title><link>/user-guide/aws/lambda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/lambda/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Lambda is a Serverless Function as a Service (FaaS) platform that lets you run code in your preferred programming language on the AWS ecosystem. AWS Lambda automatically scales your code to meet demand and handles server provisioning, management, and maintenance. AWS Lambda allows you to break down your application into smaller, independent functions that integrate seamlessly with AWS services.
LocalStack allows you to use the Lambda APIs to create, deploy, and test your Lambda functions.</description></item><item><title>OpenSearch Service</title><link>/user-guide/aws/opensearch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/opensearch/</guid><description>Introduction OpenSearch Service is an open-source search and analytics engine, offering developers and organizations advanced search capabilities, robust data analysis, and insightful visualizations. OpenSearch Service also offers log analytics, real-time application monitoring, and clickstream analysis.
LocalStack allows you to use the OpenSearch Service APIs in your local environment to create, manage, and operate the OpenSearch clusters. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of OpenSearch&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Redshift</title><link>/user-guide/aws/redshift/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/redshift/</guid><description>Introduction RedShift is a cloud-based data warehouse solution which allows end users to aggregate huge volumes of data and parallel processing of data. RedShift is fully managed by AWS and serves as a petabyte-scale service which allows users to create visualization reports and critically analyze collected data. The query results can be saved to an S3 Data Lake while additional analytics can be provided by Athena or SageMaker.
LocalStack allows you to use the RedShift APIs in your local environment to analyze structured and semi-structured data across local data warehouses and data lakes.</description></item><item><title>Resource Groups</title><link>/user-guide/aws/resource_groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/resource_groups/</guid><description>Introduction Resource Groups allow developers to organize and manage their AWS resources more efficiently. Resource Groups allow for a unified view of their resources allowing developers to perform specific actions, such as resource tagging, access control, and policy enforcement across multiple resources simultaneously. Resource Groups in AWS provide two types of queries that developers can use to build groups: Tag-based queries and CloudFormation stack-based queries. With Tag-based queries, developers can organize resources based on common attributes or characteristics, while CloudFormation stack-based queries allow developers to group resources that are deployed together as part of a CloudFormation stack.</description></item><item><title>Route 53</title><link>/user-guide/aws/route53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/route53/</guid><description>Introduction Route 53 is a highly scalable and reliable domain name system (DNS) web service provided by Amazon Web Services. Route 53 allows you to register domain names, and associate them with IP addresses or other resources. In addition to basic DNS functionality, Route 53 offers advanced features like health checks and DNS failover. Route 53 integrates seamlessly with other AWS services, such as route traffic to CloudFront distributions, S3 buckets configured for static website hosting, EC2 instances, and more.</description></item><item><title>Route 53 Resolver</title><link>/user-guide/aws/route53resolver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/route53resolver/</guid><description>Introduction Route 53 Resolver allows you to route DNS queries between your virtual private cloud (VPC) and your network. Route 53 Resolver forwards DNS queries for domain names to the appropriate DNS service based on the configuration you set up. Route 53 Resolver can be used to resolve domain names between your VPC and your network, and to resolve domain names between your VPCs.
LocalStack allows you to use the Route 53 Resolver endpoints in your local environment.</description></item><item><title>Secrets Manager</title><link>/user-guide/aws/secretsmanager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/secretsmanager/</guid><description>Introduction Secrets Manager is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to securely store, manage, and retrieve sensitive information such as passwords, API keys, and other credentials. Secrets Manager integrates seamlessly with AWS services, making it easier to manage secrets used by various applications and services. Secrets Manager supports automatic secret rotation, replacing long-term secrets with short-term ones to mitigate the risk of compromise without requiring application updates.</description></item><item><title>Security Token Service (STS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/sts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/sts/</guid><description>Introduction Security Token Service (STS) is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to grant temporary, limited-privilege credentials to users and applications. STS implements fine-grained access control and reduce the exposure of your long-term credentials. The temporary credentials, known as security tokens, can be used to access AWS services and resources based on the permissions specified in the associated policies.
LocalStack allows you to use the STS APIs in your local environment to request security tokens, manage permissions, integrate with identity providers, and more.</description></item><item><title>Simple Email Service (SES)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/ses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/ses/</guid><description>Introduction Simple Email Service (SES) is an emailing service that can be integrated with other cloud-based services. It provides API to facilitate email templating, sending bulk emails and more.
The supported APIs are available on the API coverage page for SESv1 and SESv2.
Note Users on Free plan can use SES V1 APIs in LocalStack for basic mocking and testing. For advanced features like SMTP integration and other emulation capabilities, please refer to the Ultimate plan.</description></item><item><title>Simple Notification Service (SNS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/sns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/sns/</guid><description>Introduction Simple Notification Service (SNS) is a serverless messaging service that can distribute a massive number of messages to multiple subscribers and can be used to send messages to mobile devices, email addresses, and HTTP(s) endpoints. SNS employs the Publish/Subscribe, an asynchronous messaging pattern that decouples services that produce events from services that process events.
LocalStack allows you to use the SNS APIs in your local environment to coordinate the delivery of messages to subscribing endpoints or clients.</description></item><item><title>Simple Queue Service (SQS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/sqs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/sqs/</guid><description>Introduction Simple Queue Service (SQS) is a managed messaging service offered by AWS. It allows you to decouple different components of your applications by enabling asynchronous communication through message queues. SQS allows you to reliably send, store, and receive messages with support for standard and FIFO queues.
LocalStack allows you to use the SQS APIs in your local environment to integrate and decouple distributed systems via hosted queues. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of SQS&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Simple Storage Service (S3)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/s3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/s3/</guid><description>Introduction Simple Storage Service (S3) is an object storage service that provides a highly scalable and durable solution for storing and retrieving data. In S3, a bucket represents a directory, while an object corresponds to a file. Each object or file within S3 encompasses essential attributes such as a unique key denoting its name, the actual content it holds, a version ID for versioning support, and accompanying metadata. S3 can store unlimited objects, allowing you to store, retrieve, and manage your data in a highly adaptable and reliable manner.</description></item><item><title>Simple Workflow Service (SWF)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/swf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/swf/</guid><description>Introduction Simple Workflow Service (SWF) is a fully managed service offered by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to build and manage applications with distributed components and complex workflows. SWF allows you to define workflows in a way that&amp;rsquo;s separate from the actual application code, making it easier to modify and adapt workflows without changing the application logic. SWF also provides a programming framework to design, coordinate, and execute workflows that involve multiple tasks, steps, and decision points.</description></item><item><title>Step Functions</title><link>/user-guide/aws/stepfunctions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/stepfunctions/</guid><description>Introduction Step Functions is a serverless workflow engine that enables the orchestrating of multiple AWS services. It provides a JSON-based structured language called Amazon States Language (ASL) which allows to specify how to manage a sequence of tasks and actions that compose the application&amp;rsquo;s workflow. Thus making it easier to build and maintain complex and distributed applications.
LocalStack allows you to use the Step Functions APIs in your local environment to create, execute, update, and delete state machines locally.</description></item><item><title>Support</title><link>/user-guide/aws/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/support/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Support is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that offers technical assistance and resources to help you optimize your AWS environment, troubleshoot issues, and maintain operational efficiency. Support APIs provide programmatic access to AWS Support services, including the ability to create and manage support cases programmatically. You can further automate your support workflow using various AWS services, such as Lambda, CloudWatch, and EventBridge.
LocalStack allows you to use the Support APIs in your local environment to create and manage new cases, while testing your configurations locally.</description></item><item><title>Systems Manager (SSM)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/ssm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/ssm/</guid><description>Introduction Systems Manager (SSM) is a management service provided by Amazon Web Services that helps you effectively manage and control your infrastructure resources. SSM simplifies tasks related to system and application management, patching, configuration, and automation, allowing you to maintain the health and compliance of your environment.
LocalStack allows you to use the SSM APIs in your local environment to run operational tasks on the Dockerized instances. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of SSM&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Transcribe</title><link>/user-guide/aws/transcribe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/transcribe/</guid><description>Introduction Transcribe is a service provided by AWS that offers automatic speech recognition (ASR) capabilities. It enables developers to convert spoken language into written text, making it valuable for a wide range of applications, from transcription services to voice analytics.
LocalStack allows you to use the Transcribe APIs for offline speech-to-text jobs in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API Coverage Page, which provides information on the extent of Transcribe integration with LocalStack.</description></item></channel></rss>