<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Terraform on Docs</title><link>/tags/terraform/</link><description>Recent content in Terraform on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/terraform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Host a static website locally using Simple Storage Service (S3) and Terraform with LocalStack</title><link>/tutorials/s3-static-website-terraform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/s3-static-website-terraform/</guid><description>AWS Simple Storage Service (S3) is a proprietary object storage solution that can store an unlimited number of objects for many use cases. S3 is a highly scalable, durable and reliable service that we can use for various use cases: hosting a static site, handling big data analytics, managing application logs, storing web assets and much more!
With S3, you have unlimited storage with your data stored in buckets. A bucket refers to a directory, while an object is just another term for a file.</description></item><item><title>How To: Collaborative AWS local development with LocalStack’s Cloud Pods</title><link>/tutorials/cloud-pods-collaborative-debugging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/cloud-pods-collaborative-debugging/</guid><description>Introduction By replicating environments, teams can share the exact conditions under which a bug occurs.
For developing AWS applications locally, the tool of choice is LocalStack, which can sustain a full-blown comprehensive stack. However, when issues appear, and engineers need a second opinion from a colleague, recreating the environment from scratch can leave details slipping through the cracks. This is where Cloud Pods come in, to encapsulate the state of the LocalStack instance and allow for seamless collaboration.</description></item><item><title>How To: Terraform Init Hooks for Automation &amp; Production-Identical Test Environments</title><link>/tutorials/using-terraform-with-testcontainers-and-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/using-terraform-with-testcontainers-and-localstack/</guid><description>Introduction: The importance of integration testing and how to streamline it LocalStack is a robust tool that emulates a local AWS cloud stack, allowing engineers to test and develop apps using AWS services directly on their local environments. This tool is essential for enhancing developer experience, reducing development costs and increasing efficiency.
In LocalStack, initialization hooks are scripts that customize or initialize your LocalStack instance at different stages of its lifecycle.</description></item></channel></rss>