<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on Docs</title><link>/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installation</title><link>/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>LocalStack CLI The quickest way get started with LocalStack is by using the LocalStack CLI. It allows you to start LocalStack from your command line. Please make sure that you have a working Docker installation on your machine before moving on.
Installing LocalStack CLI The CLI starts and manages the LocalStack Docker container. For alternative methods of managing the LocalStack container, see our alternative installation instructions.
Linux MacOS Windows Other/Python You can download the pre-built binary for your architecture using the link below: x86-64&amp;nbsp;ARM64&amp;nbsp; or use the curl commands below: For x86-64: $ curl --output localstack-cli-4.</description></item><item><title>Auth Token</title><link>/getting-started/auth-token/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/auth-token/</guid><description>Introduction The Auth Token identifies and authenticates users outside the LocalStack Web Application to activate the LocalStack core cloud emulator. It primarily accesses your workspace and advanced services &amp;amp; features.
Auth tokens come in two types: a Developer Auth Token and a CI Auth Token:
The Developer Auth Token is linked to a specific user within a specific workspace. Every user has their own Auth Token. It cannot be deleted but can be rotated for security reasons if needed.</description></item><item><title>Quickstart</title><link>/getting-started/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/quickstart/</guid><description>Introduction In this quickstart guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process of starting LocalStack on your local machine and deploying a serverless image resizer application that utilizes several AWS services. This guide aims to help you understand how to use LocalStack for the development and testing of your AWS applications locally. It introduces you to the following key concepts:
Starting a LocalStack instance on your local machine. Deploying an AWS serverless application infrastructure locally.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>/getting-started/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/faq/</guid><description>LocalStack Core FAQs How do I resolve SSL issues due to revoked local certificate for localhost.localstack.cloud? To resolve the issue follow the steps:
Update to the latest LocalStack version: To resolve the SSL issues due to revoked certificate, we strongly recommend updating to the latest LocalStack version (v3.7.0 and above)for the most reliable and seamless experience. Clear the cached certificate: It’s important to clear the cached certificate if you continue to experience the issue when updating to the latest LS version.</description></item><item><title>Help &amp; Support</title><link>/getting-started/help-and-support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/getting-started/help-and-support/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack provides various support channels to help users troubleshoot issues and integrate the platform into their workflows. The level of support available depends on the plan associated with your account.
Our team assists with:
Troubleshooting LocalStack-specific issues Feature usage and functionality questions Integration guidance for using LocalStack in your application Best practices for working with LocalStack services For non-technical issues, such as billing or account inquiries, please contact support via support@localstack.</description></item></channel></rss>