<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs – LocalStack 101</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack 101 on Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/academy/localstack-101/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Academy: Course Overview</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/course-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/course-overview/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Academy: What is LocalStack</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/what-is-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/what-is-localstack/</guid><description>
&lt;p>In this lesson, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about LocalStack:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The revolutionary platform that brings cloud testing to your local machine, simplifying the development process.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A drop-in replacement for AWS, ships as a user-friendly Docker image, ensuring effortless installation and setup.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Supports over 70 AWS services and capable of a diverse range of functionalities, including compute (Lambda, ECS, EKS), various database (DynamoDB, RDS, DocumentDB), and messaging services (SQS, Kinesis, MSK).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tackles sophisticated and exotic APIs (QLDB, Athena, Glue) and helps enhance your skill set.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Contains advanced collaboration features and seamless CI integrations that foster team productivity.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Our mission is to empower developers with control over their environments, eliminating time-consuming cloud dev and test loops.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>You can focus on developing exceptional products to solve real-world challenges with LocalStack as your game-changing companion.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Embrace the future of cloud development and have fun exploring!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Further reading:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://localstack.cloud/">An overview of LocalStack&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/overview">LocalStack Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/aws/feature-coverage/">LocalStack Service Coverage&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/developer/learning/">Learning Resources for Everything AWS&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/">Documentation for AWS Services&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Academy: Why LocalStack</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/why-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/why-localstack/</guid><description>
&lt;p>Let&amp;rsquo;s imagine this scenario: Alice, a software developer, takes on the task of creating a serverless
Web application on AWS Cloud. However, she faces slow and tedious development due to cloud dependencies (DBs, VMs, MQs, etc.).
Every local change needs to be packaged and uploaded to the cloud for testing.
The solution for her trouble is LocalStack — a revolutionary platform that brings cloud resources to her
local machine, enabling efficient development and testing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>LocalStack is the ultimate platform for cloud developers, offering a wide array of benefits to enhance productivity, reduce costs, and simplify maintenance.
This comprehensive course will equip you with the knowledge and skills to harness LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s power and revolutionize your cloud development workflow.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Key Takeaways:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Developer Productivity:
Witness significant time savings as LocalStack eliminates deployment bottlenecks.
Learn from real-world examples, where developers can save hours in a day by deploying changes faster.
Experience LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s incredible performance, as benchmarked against managed streams for Kafka, delivering up to 60x faster.
Say goodbye to dependencies on infrastructure teams for resource access.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cost Efficiency:
Discover how LocalStack cuts down maintenance expenses by streamlining multiple environments (staging, development, testing).&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Simplified Maintenance:
Embrace a hassle-free cloud development experience as DevOps teams experience less overhead managing cloud infrastructure and services for developers.
Unleash your cloud development potential with LocalStack and join our course to become a cloud development master.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Further reading:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://circleci.com/blog/what-is-end-to-end-testing/#c-consent-modal">The Importance of End-to-End Testing&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/compute/getting-started-with-testing-serverless-applications/">Testing Serverless Applications&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html">How Understanding Billing is Complicated and Risky&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/ci/">LocalStack in CI&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/integrations/">Third Party Integrations&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Academy: Getting started</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/getting-started/</guid><description>
&lt;p>There are several LocalStack installation methods to kickstart your cloud development journey.
Discover multiple pathways to initiate your LocalStack experience:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You&amp;rsquo;ll understand the diverse approaches to LocalStack installation:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Quickstart with LocalStack CLI:&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Install &lt;code>awscli-local&lt;/code> and &lt;code>localstack&lt;/code> via &lt;code>pip install&lt;/code>. On macOS you can use &lt;code>brew install&lt;/code>.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Start LocalStack using &lt;code>localstack start&lt;/code>.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Create a bucket and list buckets using &lt;code>awslocal s3 mb s3://test&lt;/code> and &lt;code>awslocal s3 ls&lt;/code>.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;ol start="2">
&lt;li>Alternative - Docker: Dive into an alternate installation method using Docker: pull the image and run it, it&amp;rsquo;s that easy.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Docker Compose: Explore yet another approach via Docker Compose.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>Further reading:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/overview/">Getting Started with LocalStack&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.docker.com/get-started/">Better Understanding the Concepts of Image, Container, and Quickly Getting Started with Docker&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cli/">What is AWS CLI&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/integrations/aws-cli/">What is AWS CLI local&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://pypi.org/project/pip/">Pip Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.docker.com/get-started/08_using_compose/">Docker Compose Docs&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Academy: Web App and Resource Browser</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/web-app-resource-browser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/web-app-resource-browser/</guid><description>
&lt;p>In this informative video we guide you through the essential steps of the LocalStack platform:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Witness the seamless login flow and discover how to configure the web app.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Learn how to effortlessly connect your LocalStack Account to enable a smooth integration experience.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Explore the Resource Browser as we demonstrate how to list and create fundamental resources.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To create an account for LocalStack, visit &lt;a href="https://app.localstack.cloud/sign-up">app.localstack.cloud/sign-up&lt;/a>. You can sign up with your email address or one of our supported social identity providers (such as GitHub).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Further reading:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/web-application/">Web App Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/web-application/resource-browser/">Resource Browser&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Academy: Full Project Demo</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/full-project-demo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/full-project-demo/</guid><description>
&lt;p>Discover the ins and outs of one of our Developer Hub&amp;rsquo;s practical sample applications—a note-taking platform.
This video tutorial offers a comprehensive walk-through, beginning with the checkout of the GitHub project and
culminating in deploying the operational application on LocalStack. Covering the essentials, we&amp;rsquo;ll guide you
through dependency installation, backend and frontend build, and a detailed exploration of the application&amp;rsquo;s service
diagram to unveil the integral components at play.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Further exploring:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/applications">LocalStack Developer Hub Applications&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Academy: Cloud Pods and Collaborative Work</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/cloud-pods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/cloud-pods/</guid><description>
&lt;p>This video will cover:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What are Cloud Pods ?&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Unveil the concept of Cloud Pods, designed to capture a persistent snapshot of LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s application state.
Deviate from the default ephemeral state by leveraging Cloud Pods&amp;rsquo; capability to preserve data across restarts.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>How are cloud pods useful ?&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Gain insight into the advantages they offer, including the creation of shareable local cloud sandboxes.
Learn about the collaborative potential of distributing and sharing pods among team members and discover
how Cloud Pods contribute to reproducibility in applications and pre-seeding test environments.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Demo&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Dive into a concise yet impactful demo that brings Cloud Pods to life.
Witness firsthand how they empower developers in various scenarios, especially for collaboration.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;br/>
Further reading:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/tools/cloud-pods/">Cloud Pods Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://docs.localstack.cloud/user-guide/web-application/cloud-pods-browser/">Cloud Pods Browser&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>