<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LocalStack 101 on Docs</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack 101 on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/academy/localstack-101/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Course Overview</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/course-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/course-overview/</guid><description/></item><item><title>What is LocalStack</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/what-is-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/what-is-localstack/</guid><description>In this lesson, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about LocalStack:
The revolutionary platform that brings cloud testing to your local machine, simplifying the development process. A drop-in replacement for AWS, ships as a user-friendly Docker image, ensuring effortless installation and setup. Supports over 70 AWS services and capable of a diverse range of functionalities, including compute (Lambda, ECS, EKS), various database (DynamoDB, RDS, DocumentDB), and messaging services (SQS, Kinesis, MSK). Tackles sophisticated and exotic APIs (QLDB, Athena, Glue) and helps enhance your skill set.</description></item><item><title>Why LocalStack</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/why-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/why-localstack/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s imagine this scenario: Alice, a software developer, takes on the task of creating a serverless Web application on AWS Cloud. However, she faces slow and tedious development due to cloud dependencies (DBs, VMs, MQs, etc.). Every local change needs to be packaged and uploaded to the cloud for testing. The solution for her trouble is LocalStack — a revolutionary platform that brings cloud resources to her local machine, enabling efficient development and testing.</description></item><item><title>Getting started</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/getting-started/</guid><description>There are several LocalStack installation methods to kickstart your cloud development journey. Discover multiple pathways to initiate your LocalStack experience:
You&amp;rsquo;ll understand the diverse approaches to LocalStack installation:
Quickstart with LocalStack CLI: Install awscli-local and localstack via pip install. On macOS you can use brew install. Start LocalStack using localstack start. Create a bucket and list buckets using awslocal s3 mb s3://test and awslocal s3 ls. Alternative - Docker: Dive into an alternate installation method using Docker: pull the image and run it, it&amp;rsquo;s that easy.</description></item><item><title>Web App and Resource Browser</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/web-app-resource-browser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/web-app-resource-browser/</guid><description>In this informative video we guide you through the essential steps of the LocalStack platform:
Witness the seamless login flow and discover how to configure the web app. Learn how to effortlessly connect your LocalStack Account to enable a smooth integration experience. Explore the Resource Browser as we demonstrate how to list and create fundamental resources. To create an account for LocalStack, visit app.localstack.cloud/sign-up. You can sign up with your email address or one of our supported social identity providers (such as GitHub).</description></item><item><title>Full Project Demo</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/full-project-demo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/full-project-demo/</guid><description>Discover the ins and outs of one of our Developer Hub&amp;rsquo;s practical sample applications—a note-taking platform. This video tutorial offers a comprehensive walk-through, beginning with the checkout of the GitHub project and culminating in deploying the operational application on LocalStack. Covering the essentials, we&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through dependency installation, backend and frontend build, and a detailed exploration of the application&amp;rsquo;s service diagram to unveil the integral components at play.
Further exploring:</description></item><item><title>Cloud Pods and Collaborative Work</title><link>/academy/localstack-101/cloud-pods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/academy/localstack-101/cloud-pods/</guid><description>This video will cover:
What are Cloud Pods ?
Unveil the concept of Cloud Pods, designed to capture a persistent snapshot of LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s application state. Deviate from the default ephemeral state by leveraging Cloud Pods&amp;rsquo; capability to preserve data across restarts. How are cloud pods useful ?
Gain insight into the advantages they offer, including the creation of shareable local cloud sandboxes. Learn about the collaborative potential of distributing and sharing pods among team members and discover how Cloud Pods contribute to reproducibility in applications and pre-seeding test environments.</description></item></channel></rss>