<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise on Docs</title><link>/tags/enterprise/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enterprise Image</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-image/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack offers an Enterprise image that allows offline usage and includes a customer-specific configuration. This offline functionality is enabled by:
Pre-installed packages required for running specific services that are usually downloaded on demand (such as opensearch or dynamodb-local). A certificate keypair for localhost.localstack.cloud to resolve to the LocalStack container via our DNS server. An embedded decryption key in the image, eliminating the need to contact the license server to operate LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>SSO for Azure AD</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/single-sign-on/azure-ad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/single-sign-on/azure-ad/</guid><description>To configure SSO with an Azure AD Enterprise application, we provide a simple step-by-step solution below:
Navigate to &amp;ldquo;Set up single sign on&amp;rdquo; in your Azure AD Enterprise application.
In the Basic SAML Configuration, ensure that the settings match the following details
Take the correct values for Identifier (Entity ID) and Reply URL from the Identity Provider configuration page.
In the Attributes &amp;amp; Claims section, add a group claim with the following configuration and save it.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Support</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-support/</guid><description>Introduction Enterprise support offers organizations personalized resources, direct communication channels with the LocalStack team, and flexible service level agreements (SLAs) to meet specific business requirements. The key components of our enterprise support offering include:
Direct Slack Connect Channel: A dedicated Slack Connect channel is available to maintain a direct communication link with the LocalStack engineering team. This setup ensures quick issue resolution and streamlined collaboration, improving overall service efficiency. Dedicated Customer Success Manager (CSM) and Technical Account Manager (TAM): Enterprise customers are assigned a CSM and SA.</description></item><item><title>Single-Sign On</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/single-sign-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/single-sign-on/</guid><description>Custom Single-Sign On (SSO) Identity providers, can be enabled to facilitate the process of quickly onboarding team members from your organization.
In order to configure SSO access, first sign in to the LocalStack Web application under app.localstack.cloud. In your profile settings, navigate to the Single Sign-on tab which will list existing SSO Identity Providers (if any exist).
Next, click the button to create a new identity provider (IdP), where you can choose between the two leading industry standards:</description></item></channel></rss>