<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs – Persistence</title><link>/categories/persistence/</link><description>Recent content in Persistence on Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/categories/persistence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tools: Cloud Pods</title><link>/tools/cloud-pods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/cloud-pods/</guid><description>
&lt;p>Local Cloud Pods are a mechanism that allows you to take a snapshot of your local instance, persist it to a storage backend (e.g., git repository), and easily share it out with your team members.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can create and manage Local Cloud Pods via the Web UI, and in order to load and store the persistent state of pods, you can use the &lt;code>localstack&lt;/code> command line interface (CLI).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Below is a simple example of how you can push and pull Local Cloud Pods using the &lt;code>localstack&lt;/code> CLI:&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash">&lt;span style="color:#8f5902;font-style:italic"># User 1 pushes state of Cloud Pod to persistent server&lt;/span>
$ awslocal kinesis list-streams
&lt;span style="color:#ce5c00;font-weight:bold">{&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;StreamNames&amp;#34;&lt;/span>: &lt;span style="color:#ce5c00;font-weight:bold">[&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;mystream123&amp;#34;&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#ce5c00;font-weight:bold">]}&lt;/span>
$ localstack pod push mypod1
...
&lt;span style="color:#8f5902;font-style:italic"># User 2 pulls state from the server to local instance&lt;/span>
$ localstack pod pull mypod1
$ awslocal kinesis list-streams
&lt;span style="color:#ce5c00;font-weight:bold">{&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;StreamNames&amp;#34;&lt;/span>: &lt;span style="color:#ce5c00;font-weight:bold">[&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#4e9a06">&amp;#34;mystream123&amp;#34;&lt;/span>&lt;span style="color:#ce5c00;font-weight:bold">]}&lt;/span>
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>
&lt;div class="alert alert-info" role="alert">
&lt;h4 class="alert-heading">Persistence configuration&lt;/h4>
Using local Cloud pods requires setting the &lt;code>DATA_DIR&lt;/code> configuration variable to point to a folder on your local machine - this folder will be used to persist and load the state of cloud pods in your local instance.
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>Local Cloud Pods support different storage mechanisms - currently we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on using &lt;code>git&lt;/code> repositories as the storage backend, as &lt;code>git&lt;/code> is often readily available on developers' machines and is easy to integrate with (no additional access control settings required).
Support for more storage backends is coming soon (e.g., S3 buckets, FTP servers, etc.).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can use the &lt;a href="https://app.localstack.cloud/pods">LocalStack Web UI&lt;/a> to create a new Local Cloud Pod (make sure to adjust the Git URL and branch name to point to your repository):&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="cloudPodsUI.png" alt="Local Cloud Pods UI">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Once the pod has been created, can use the CLI to log in and list the pod in your terminal:
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre style="background-color:#f8f8f8;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4">&lt;code class="language-text" data-lang="text">&lt;span class="command-prefix">$ &lt;/span>export LOCALSTACK_API_KEY=...
&lt;span class="command-prefix">$ &lt;/span>localstack login
...
&lt;span class="command-prefix">$ &lt;/span>localstack pod list
Name Backend URL Size State
------ --------- --------------------------------- ------ -------
pod1 git ssh://git@github.com/your_org/... 1.68MB Shared&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="alert alert-info" role="alert">
&lt;h4 class="alert-heading">LocalStack Pro feature&lt;/h4>
Cloud Pods are a feature of LocalStack Pro.
Please ensure that the &lt;code>LOCALSTACK_API_KEY&lt;/code> is properly configured.
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>After the pod definition has been created, you should be able to use the &lt;code>push&lt;/code>/&lt;code>pull&lt;/code> commands listed above to push and pull the pod state to the Git repo.
After pulling the pod, LocalStack will automatically inject pod state in your instance at runtime without requiring a restart.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In some cases, you may want to reset your current application state before pulling a pod.
This can be achieved by manually deleting the &lt;code>DATA_DIR&lt;/code> and restarting the application with the &lt;code>localstack pod reset&lt;/code> command.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="alert alert-info" role="alert">
&lt;h4 class="alert-heading">Backup your state&lt;/h4>
If you &lt;code>pull&lt;/code> a Local Cloud Pod, it will attempt to merge the stored pod state with the existing state in your LocalStack instance.
Please make sure to create a backup of any data before pulling a cloud pod, if required.
&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>