<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ultimate on Docs</title><link>/tags/ultimate/</link><description>Recent content in Ultimate on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/ultimate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>K8s Operator</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/k8s-operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/k8s-operator/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack K8s operator is a custom Kubernetes operator that offers LocalStack emulator as a native resource in Kubernetes environments. The operator is designed to simplify the deployment and management of LocalStack in Kubernetes clusters.
Installation To install the K8s operator, run the following commands:
$ kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/localstack/localstack-k8s-operator/v0.2.0/release/crds.yaml $ kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/localstack/localstack-k8s-operator/v0.2.0/release/controller.yaml You can then deploy a LocalStack instance by storing the following file content as localstack.yml and applying it against the cluster via kubectl apply -f localstack.</description></item><item><title>IAM Policy Stream</title><link>/user-guide/security-testing/iam-policy-stream/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/security-testing/iam-policy-stream/</guid><description>Introduction The IAM Policy Stream generates a steady stream of policies along with their corresponding principals or resources. When a request is made, it initially displays the principal or resource to which the policy will be attached. This is typically a service resource for resource-based policies, or an IAM principal for other cases. Subsequently, it displays the suggested policy. This feature aids in identifying the correct permissions for cloud applications and can help spot logical errors, such as unexpected actions in a policy.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Executor</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/kubernetes-executor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/kubernetes-executor/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Enterprise provides a Kubernetes executor for various emulated services. It allows you to run these services as Kubernetes pods in your Kubernetes clusters. By default, LocalStack uses the docker backend for these services. You can use either service-specific configuration variables or the generic CONTAINER_RUNTIME variable set to kubernetes to enable the Kubernetes executor.
EC2 Kubernetes Executor The LocalStack Enterprise image allows you to run EC2 instances on Kubernetes. You can do so by setting the EC2_VM_MANAGER environment variable to kubernetes in the LocalStack container.</description></item><item><title>AWS Replicator</title><link>/user-guide/tools/aws-replicator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/tools/aws-replicator/</guid><description>Introduction Infrastructure deployed on AWS often requires access to shared resources defined externally. For example a VPC defined by another team to contain the application infrastructure. This makes it harder to deploy applications into LocalStack as these resource dependencies must be deployed first. These dependencies may not live in IaC where deployment is easy, or accessing the IaC may not be easy. Some resources may be referred to by ARN, for example Secrets Manager secrets, but these ARNs are partly random meaning that simply creating a new resource in LocalStack will generate a resource with a different ARN.</description></item><item><title>Account Management</title><link>/user-guide/aws/account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/account/</guid><description>Introduction The Account service provides APIs to manage your AWS account. You can use the Account APIs to retrieve information about your account, manage your contact information and alternate contacts. Additionally, you can use the Account APIs to enable or disable a region for your account, and delete alternate contacts in your account.
LocalStack allows you to use the Account API to retrieve information about your account. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of Account&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Amplify</title><link>/user-guide/aws/amplify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/amplify/</guid><description>Introduction Amplify is a JavaScript-based development framework with libraries, UI components, and a standard CLI interface for building and deploying web and mobile applications. With Amplify, developers can build and host static websites, single-page applications, and full-stack serverless web applications using an abstraction layer over popular AWS services like DynamoDB, Cognito, AppSync, Lambda, S3, and more.
LocalStack allows you to use the Amplify APIs to build and test their Amplify applications locally.</description></item><item><title>AppSync</title><link>/user-guide/aws/appsync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/appsync/</guid><description>Introduction AppSync is a managed service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to create serverless GraphQL APIs to query databases, microservices, and other APIs. AppSync allows you to define your data models and business logic using a declarative approach, and connect to various data sources, including other AWS services, relational databases, and custom data sources.
LocalStack allows you to use the AppSync APIs in your local environment to connect your applications and services to data and events.</description></item><item><title>Athena</title><link>/user-guide/aws/athena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/athena/</guid><description>Introduction Athena is an interactive query service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to analyze data stored in S3 using standard SQL queries. Athena allows users to create ad-hoc queries to perform data analysis, filter, aggregate, and join datasets stored in S3. It supports various file formats, such as JSON, Parquet, and CSV, making it compatible with a wide range of data sources.
LocalStack allows you to configure the Athena APIs with a Hive metastore that can connect to the S3 API and query your data directly in your local environment.</description></item><item><title>AWS Fault Injection Service</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/fault-injection-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/fault-injection-service/</guid><description>The Fault Injection Service (FIS) is a fully managed service by AWS designed to help you improve the resilience of your applications by simulating real-world outages and operational issues. This service allows you to conduct controlled experiments on your AWS infrastructure, injecting faults and observing how your system responds under various conditions.
By using the Fault Injection Service, you can identify weaknesses, test recovery procedures, and ensure that your applications can withstand unexpected disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Backup</title><link>/user-guide/aws/backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/backup/</guid><description>Introduction Backup is a centralized backup service provided by Amazon Web Services. It simplifies the process of backing up and restoring your data across various AWS services and resources. Backup supports a wide range of AWS resources, including Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes, Relational Database Service (RDS) databases, DynamoDB tables, Elastic File System (EFS) file systems, and more. Backup enables you to set backup retention policies, allowing you to specify how long you want to retain your backup copies.</description></item><item><title>Batch</title><link>/user-guide/aws/batch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/batch/</guid><description>Introduction Batch is a cloud-based service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that simplifies the process of running batch computing workloads on the AWS cloud infrastructure. Batch allows you to efficiently process large volumes of data and run batch jobs without the need to manage and provision underlying compute resources.
LocalStack allows you to use the Batch APIs to automate and scale computational tasks in your local environment while handling batch workloads.</description></item><item><title>Bedrock</title><link>/user-guide/aws/bedrock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/bedrock/</guid><description>Introduction Bedrock is a fully managed service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that makes foundation models from various LLM providers accessible via an API. LocalStack allows you to use the Bedrock APIs to test and develop AI-powered applications in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API Coverage Page, which provides information on the extent of Bedrock&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.
Getting started This guide is designed for users new to AWS Bedrock and assumes basic knowledge of the AWS CLI and our awslocal wrapper script.</description></item><item><title>Chaos API</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-api/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Chaos API allows you to mimic outages across any AWS region or service. Intentionally triggering service outages and monitoring the system&amp;rsquo;s response in situations where the infrastructure is compromised offers a powerful way to test. This strategy helps gauge the effectiveness of the system&amp;rsquo;s deployment procedures and its resilience against infrastructure disruptions, which is a key element of chaos engineering.
You can use LocalStack Chaos API to cause API failures for any combination of the following:</description></item><item><title>Chaos Engineering Dashboard</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-application-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-application-dashboard/</guid><description>Introduction The Chaos Engineering Dashboard in LocalStack offers streamlined testing for cloud applications, enabling you to simulate server errors, service outages, regional disruptions, and network latency with ease, ensuring your app is ready for real-world challenges.
The dashboard uses LocalStack Chaos API under the hood to offer a set of customizable templates that can be seamlessly integrated into any automation workflows.
You can find this feature in the LocalStack Web Application by navigating to app.</description></item><item><title>CloudTrail</title><link>/user-guide/aws/cloudtrail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/cloudtrail/</guid><description>Introduction CloudTrail is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to track and monitor all activities and events within your AWS environment. It records API calls and actions made on your AWS resources, offering an audit trail that helps you understand changes, diagnose issues, and maintain compliance.
LocalStack allows you to use the CloudTrail APIs in your local environment to create and manage Event history and trails.</description></item><item><title>CodeDeploy</title><link>/user-guide/aws/codedeploy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/codedeploy/</guid><description>Introduction CodeDeploy is a service that automates application deployments. On AWS, it supports deployments to Amazon EC2 instances, on-premises instances, serverless Lambda functions, or Amazon ECS services. Furthermore, based on the target it is also possible to use an in-place deployment or a blue/green deployment.
LocalStack supports a mocking of CodeDeploy API operations. The supported operations are listed on the API coverage page.
Getting Started This guide will walk through the process of creating CodeDeploy applications, deployment configuration, deployment groups, and deployments.</description></item><item><title>CodePipeline</title><link>/user-guide/aws/codepipeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/codepipeline/</guid><description>Introduction CodePipeline is a continuous integration/continuous delivery (CI/CD) service offered by AWS. CodePipeline can be used to create automated pipelines that handle the build, test and deployment of software.
LocalStack comes with a bespoke execution engine that can be used to create, manage, and execute pipelines. It supports a variety of actions that integrate with S3, CodeBuild, CodeConnections, and more. The available operations can be found on the API coverage page.</description></item><item><title>Cost Explorer</title><link>/user-guide/aws/ce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/ce/</guid><description>Introduction Cost Explorer is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to visualize, analyze, and manage your AWS spending and usage. Cost Explorer offers options to filter and group data by dimensions such as service, region, instance type, and more. With Cost Explorer, you can forecast costs, track budget progress, and set up alerts to receive notifications when spending exceeds predefined thresholds.
LocalStack allows you to use the Cost Explorer APIs in your local environment to create and manage cost category definition, cost anomaly monitors &amp;amp; subscriptions.</description></item><item><title>Database Migration Service (DMS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/dms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/dms/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Database Migration Service provides migration solution from databases, data warehouses, and other type of data stores (e.g. S3, SAP). The migration can be homogeneous (source and target have the same type), but often times is heterogeneous as it supports migration from various sources to various targets (self-hosted and AWS services).
LocalStack only supports selected use cases for DMS at the moment. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of DMS integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>DocumentDB (DocDB)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/docdb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/docdb/</guid><description>Introduction DocumentDB is a fully managed, non-relational database service that supports MongoDB workloads. DocumentDB is compatible with MongoDB, meaning you can use the same MongoDB drivers, applications, and tools to run, manage, and scale workloads on DocumentDB without having to worry about managing the underlying infrastructure.
LocalStack allows you to use the DocumentDB APIs to create and manage DocumentDB clusters and instances. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of DocumentDB&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Elastic Beanstalk</title><link>/user-guide/aws/elasticbeanstalk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/elasticbeanstalk/</guid><description>Introduction Elastic Beanstalk (EB) is a managed platform-as-a-service (PaaS) provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that simplifies the process of deploying, managing, and scaling web applications and services. Elastic Beanstalk orchestrates various AWS services, including EC2, S3, SNS, and Elastic Load Balancers. Elastic Beanstalk also supports various application environments, such as Java, .NET, Node.js, PHP, Python, Ruby, Go, and Docker.
LocalStack allows you to use the Elastic Beanstalk APIs in your local environment to create and manage applications, environments and versions.</description></item><item><title>Elastic File System (EFS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/efs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/efs/</guid><description>Introduction Elastic File System (EFS) is a fully managed file storage service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS). EFS offers scalable and shared file storage that can be accessed by multiple EC2 instances and on-premises servers simultaneously. EFS utilizes the Network File System protocol to allow it to be used as a data source for various applications and workloads.
LocalStack allows you to use the EFS APIs in your local environment to create local file systems, lifecycle configurations, and file system policies.</description></item><item><title>Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/eks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/eks/</guid><description>Introduction Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS) is a managed Kubernetes service that makes it easy to run Kubernetes on AWS without installing, operating, and maintaining your own Kubernetes control plane or worker nodes. Kubernetes is an open-source system for automating containerized applications&amp;rsquo; deployment, scaling, and management.
LocalStack allows you to use the EKS APIs in your local environment to spin up embedded Kubernetes clusters in your local Docker engine or use an existing Kubernetes installation you can access from your local machine (defined in $HOME/.</description></item><item><title>Elastic MapReduce (EMR)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/emr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/emr/</guid><description>Introduction Amazon Elastic MapReduce (EMR) is a fully managed big data processing service that allows developers to effortlessly create, deploy, and manage big data applications. EMR supports various big data processing frameworks, including Hadoop MapReduce, Apache Spark, Apache Hive, and Apache Pig. Developers can leverage these frameworks and their rich ecosystem of tools and libraries to perform complex data transformations, machine learning tasks, and real-time data processing.
LocalStack supports EMR and allows developers to run data analytics workloads locally.</description></item><item><title>Elemental MediaConvert</title><link>/user-guide/aws/elementalmediaconvert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/elementalmediaconvert/</guid><description>Introduction Elemental MediaConvert is a file-based video transcoding service with broadcast-grade features. It enables you to easily create high-quality video streams for broadcast and multiscreen delivery.
LocalStack allows you to mock the MediaConvert APIs in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of MediaConvert&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.
Note Elemental MediaConvert is in a preview state. Getting started This guide is designed for users new to Elemental MediaConvert and assumes basic knowledge of the AWS CLI and our awslocal wrapper script.</description></item><item><title>Elemental MediaStore</title><link>/user-guide/aws/mediastore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/mediastore/</guid><description>Introduction MediaStore is a scalable and highly available object storage service designed specifically for media content. It provides a reliable way to store, manage, and serve media assets, such as audio, video, and images, with low latency and high performance. MediaStore seamlessly integrates with other AWS services like Elemental MediaConvert, Elemental MediaLive, Elemental MediaPackage, and CloudFront.
LocalStack allows you to use the Elemental MediaStore APIs as a high-performance storage solution for media content in your local environment.</description></item><item><title>Fault Injection Service (FIS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/fis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/fis/</guid><description>Introduction Fault Injection Service (FIS) is a service provided by Amazon Web Services that enables you to test the resilience of your applications and infrastructure by injecting faults and failures into your AWS resources. FIS simulates faults such as resource unavailability and service errors to assess the impact on your application&amp;rsquo;s performance and availability. The full list of such possible fault injections is available in the AWS docs.
LocalStack allows you to use the FIS APIs in your local environment to introduce faults in other services, in order to check how your setup behaves when parts of it stop working locally.</description></item><item><title>Glacier</title><link>/user-guide/aws/glacier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/glacier/</guid><description>Introduction Glacier is a data storage service provided by Amazon Web Services to suit the long-term storage of archives and backup of infrequently accessed data. It offers various retrieval options, different levels of retrieval speed, and more. Glacier uses a Vault container to store your data, similar to how S3 stores data in Buckets. A Vault further holds the data in an Archive, which can contain text, images, video, and audio files.</description></item><item><title>Glue</title><link>/user-guide/aws/glue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/glue/</guid><description>Introduction The Glue API in LocalStack Pro allows you to run ETL (Extract-Transform-Load) jobs locally, maintaining table metadata in the local Glue data catalog, and using the Spark ecosystem (PySpark/Scala) to run data processing workflows.
LocalStack allows you to use the Glue APIs in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of Glue&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.
Note LocalStack now includes a container-based Glue Job executor, enabling Glue jobs to run within a Docker environment.</description></item><item><title>Identity Store</title><link>/user-guide/aws/identitystore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/identitystore/</guid><description>Introduction Identity Store is a managed service that enables the creation and management of groups within your AWS environment. Groups are used to manage access to AWS resources, and Identity Store provides a central location to create and manage groups across your AWS accounts.
LocalStack allows you to use the Identity Store APIs to create and manage groups in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API Coverage Page, which provides information on the extent of Identity Store integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>IoT Analytics</title><link>/user-guide/aws/iotanalytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/iotanalytics/</guid><description>Warning IoT Analytics will be retired on 15 December 2025. It will be removed from LocalStack soon after this date. Introduction IoT Analytics is a managed service that enables you to collect, store, process, and analyze data generated by your IoT devices. It provides a set of tools to build IoT applications without having to manage the underlying infrastructure.
LocalStack allows you to use the IoT Analytics APIs to create and manage channels, data stores, and pipelines in your local environment.</description></item><item><title>IoT Data</title><link>/user-guide/aws/iotdata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/iotdata/</guid><description>Introduction IoT Data provides secure, bi-directional communication between Internet-connected things, such as sensors, actuators, embedded devices, or smart appliances, and the AWS Cloud. It allows you to connect your devices to the cloud and interact with them using the AWS Management Console, AWS CLI, or AWS SDKs.
LocalStack allows you to use the IoT Data APIs to update, get, and delete the shadow of a thing in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API Coverage Page, which provides information on the extent of IoT Data integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>IoT Wireless</title><link>/user-guide/aws/iotwireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/iotwireless/</guid><description>Introduction AWS IoT Wireless is a managed service that enables customers to connect and manage wireless devices. The service provides a set of APIs to manage wireless devices, gateways, and destinations.
LocalStack allows you to use the IoT Wireless APIs in your local environment from creating wireless devices and gateways. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of IoT Wireless&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Kinesis Data Analytics for SQL Applications</title><link>/user-guide/aws/kinesisanalytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/kinesisanalytics/</guid><description>Warning Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics for SQL Applications will be retired on 27 January 2026. It will be removed from LocalStack soon after this date. Introduction Kinesis Data Analytics for SQL Applications is a service offered by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that enables you to process and analyze streaming data in real-time. It allows you to apply transformations, filtering, and enrichment to streaming data using standard SQL syntax.
LocalStack allows you to use the Kinesis Data Analytics APIs in your local environment.</description></item><item><title>Lake Formation</title><link>/user-guide/aws/lakeformation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/lakeformation/</guid><description>Introduction Lake Formation is a managed service that allows users to build, secure, and manage data lakes. Lake Formation allows users to define and enforce fine-grained access controls, manage metadata, and discover and share data across multiple data sources.
LocalStack allows you to use the Lake Formation APIs in your local environment to register resources, grant permissions, and list resources and permissions. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of Lake Formation&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Managed Blockchain (AMB)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/managedblockchain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/managedblockchain/</guid><description>Managed Blockchain (AMB) is a managed service that enables the creation and management of blockchain networks, such as Hyperledger Fabric, Bitcoin, Polygon and Ethereum. Blockchain enables the development of applications in which multiple entities can conduct transactions and exchange data securely and transparently, eliminating the requirement for a central, trusted authority.
LocalStack allows you to use the AMB APIs to develop and deploy decentralized applications in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API Coverage Page, which provides information on the extent of AMB integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Managed Service for Apache Flink</title><link>/user-guide/aws/kinesisanalyticsv2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/kinesisanalyticsv2/</guid><description>Note This service was formerly known as &amp;lsquo;Kinesis Data Analytics for Apache Flink&amp;rsquo;. Introduction Apache Flink is a framework for building applications that process and analyze streaming data. Managed Service for Apache Flink (MSF) is an AWS service that provides the underlying infrastructure and a hosted Apache Flink cluster that can run Apache Flink applications.
LocalStack lets you to run Flink applications locally and implements several AWS-compatible API operations.</description></item><item><title>Managed Streaming for Kafka (MSK)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/msk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/msk/</guid><description>Introduction Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (MSK) is a fully managed Apache Kafka service that allows you to build and run applications that process streaming data. MSK offers a centralized platform to facilitate seamless communication between various AWS services and applications through event-driven architectures, facilitating data ingestion, processing, and analytics for various applications. MSK also features automatic scaling and built-in monitoring, allowing users to build robust, high-throughput data pipelines.
LocalStack allows you to use the MSK APIs in your local environment to spin up Kafka clusters on the local machine, create topics for exchanging messages, and define event source mappings that trigger Lambda functions when messages are received on a certain topic.</description></item><item><title>Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow (MWAA)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/mwaa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/mwaa/</guid><description>Introduction Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow (MWAA) is a fully managed service by AWS that simplifies the deployment, management, and scaling of Apache Airflow workflows in the cloud. MWAA leverages the familiar Airflow features and integrations while integrating with S3, Glue, Redshift, Lambda, and other AWS services to build data pipelines and orchestrate data processing workflows in the cloud.
LocalStack allows you to use the MWAA APIs in your local environment to allow the setup and operation of data pipelines.</description></item><item><title>MemoryDB for Redis</title><link>/user-guide/aws/memorydb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/memorydb/</guid><description>Introduction MemoryDB is a fully managed, Redis-compatible, in-memory database tailored for workloads demanding ultra-fast, primary database functionality. It streamlines the deployment and management of in-memory databases within the AWS cloud environment, acting as a replacement for using a cache in front of a database for improved durability and performance.
LocalStack provides support for the main MemoryDB APIs surrounding cluster creation, allowing developers to utilize the MemoryDB functionalities in their local development environment.</description></item><item><title>Neptune</title><link>/user-guide/aws/neptune/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/neptune/</guid><description>Introduction Neptune is a fully managed, highly available, and scalable graph database service offered by AWS. It is designed for storing and querying highly connected data for applications that require complex relationship modeling, such as social networks, recommendation engines, and fraud detection. Neptune supports popular graph query languages like Gremlin and SPARQL, making it compatible with a wide range of graph applications and tools.
LocalStack allows you to use the Neptune APIs in your local environment to support both property graph and RDF graph models.</description></item><item><title>Organizations</title><link>/user-guide/aws/organizations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/organizations/</guid><description>Amazon Web Services Organizations is an account management service that allows you to consolidate multiple different AWS accounts into an organization. It allows you to manage different accounts in a single organization and consolidate billing. With Organizations, you can also attach different policies to your organizational units (OUs) or individual accounts in your organization.
Organizations is available over LocalStack Pro and the supported APIs are available over our configuration page.</description></item><item><title>Pinpoint</title><link>/user-guide/aws/pinpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/pinpoint/</guid><description>Warning Amazon Pinpoint will be retired on 30 October 2026. It will be removed from LocalStack soon after this date. Introduction Pinpoint is a customer engagement service to facilitate communication across multiple channels, including email, SMS, and push notifications. Pinpoint allows developers to create and manage customer segments based on various attributes, such as user behavior and demographics, while integrating with other AWS services to send targeted messages to customers.</description></item><item><title>Private Certificate Authority (ACM PCA)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/pca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/pca/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Private Certificate Authority (ACM PCA) is a managed private Certificate Authority (CA) service that manages the lifecycle of your private certificates. ACM PCA extends ACM&amp;rsquo;s certificate management capabilities to private certificates, enabling you to manage public and private certificates centrally.
LocalStack allows you to use the ACM PCA APIs to create, list, and delete private certificates. You can creating, describing, tagging, and listing tags for a CA using ACM PCA.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Ledger Database (QLDB)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/qldb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/qldb/</guid><description>Warning Amazon QLDB will be retired on 31 July 2025. It will be removed from LocalStack soon after this date. Introduction Amazon Quantum Ledger Database is a fully managed ledger database service offered by Amazon Web Services. It is designed to provide transparent, immutable, and cryptographically verifiable transaction log functionality to applications. QLDB is particularly useful for applications that need a secure and scalable way to maintain a complete and verifiable history of data changes over time.</description></item><item><title>Redshift</title><link>/user-guide/aws/redshift/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/redshift/</guid><description>Introduction RedShift is a cloud-based data warehouse solution which allows end users to aggregate huge volumes of data and parallel processing of data. RedShift is fully managed by AWS and serves as a petabyte-scale service which allows users to create visualization reports and critically analyze collected data. The query results can be saved to an S3 Data Lake while additional analytics can be provided by Athena or SageMaker.
LocalStack allows you to use the RedShift APIs in your local environment to analyze structured and semi-structured data across local data warehouses and data lakes.</description></item><item><title>Resource Access Manager (RAM)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/ram/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/ram/</guid><description>Introduction Resource Access Manager (RAM) helps resources to be shared across AWS accounts, within or across organizations. On AWS, RAM is an abstraction on top of AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) which can manage resource-based policies to supported resource types. The API operations supported by LocalStack can be found on the API coverage page.
Getting started Start the LocalStack container using your preferred method. This section will illustrate how to create permissions and resource shares using the AWS CLI.</description></item><item><title>SageMaker</title><link>/user-guide/aws/sagemaker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/sagemaker/</guid><description>Introduction Amazon SageMaker is a fully managed service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that provides the tools to build, train, and deploy machine-learning models in the cloud for predictive analytics applications. It streamlines the machine learning development process, reduces the time and effort required to build and deploy models, and offers the scalability and flexibility needed for large-scale machine learning projects in the AWS cloud.
LocalStack provides a local version of the SageMaker API, which allows running jobs to create machine learning models (e.</description></item><item><title>Serverless Application Repository</title><link>/user-guide/aws/serverlessrepo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/serverlessrepo/</guid><description>Introduction Serverless Application Repository allows developers to discover, deploy, and share serverless applications and components. Using Serverless Application Repository, developers can build &amp;amp; publish applications and components once and share them across the community and organizations, making them accessible to others. Serverless Application Repository provides a user-friendly interface to search, filter, and browse through a diverse catalog of serverless applications.
LocalStack allows you to use the Serverless Application Repository APIs in your local environment to create, update, delete, and list serverless applications and components.</description></item><item><title>Service Discovery</title><link>/user-guide/aws/servicediscovery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/servicediscovery/</guid><description>Introduction Service Discovery simplifies the management and discovery of services by locating and connecting to the components and resources that make up their applications. Service Discovery allows for a centralized mechanism for dynamically registering, tracking, and resolving service instances, allowing seamless communication between services. Service discovery uses Cloud Map API actions to manage HTTP and DNS namespaces for services, enabling automatic registration and discovery of services running in the cluster.</description></item><item><title>Shield</title><link>/user-guide/aws/shield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/shield/</guid><description>Introduction Shield is a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS. Shield provides always-on detection and inline mitigations that minimize application downtime and latency, by protecting users from L4, L7 and most common L3, L4 network and transport layer DDoS attacks. Shield detection and mitigation is designed to protect against threats, including ones that are not known to the service at the time of detection.</description></item><item><title>Textract</title><link>/user-guide/aws/textract/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/textract/</guid><description>Textract is a machine learning service that automatically extracts text, forms, and tables from scanned documents. It simplifies the process of extracting valuable information from a variety of document types, enabling applications to quickly analyze and understand document content.
LocalStack allows you to mock Textract APIs in your local environment. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, providing details on the extent of Textract&amp;rsquo;s integration with LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>Timestream</title><link>/user-guide/aws/timestream/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/timestream/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack contains basic support for Timestream time series databases, including these operations:
Creating databases Creating tables Writing records to tables Querying timeseries data from tables The supported APIs are available on our API Coverage Page (Timestream-Query/Timestream-Write), which provides information on the extent of Timestream integration with LocalStack.
Getting Started The following example illustrates the basic operations, using the awslocal command line.
First, we create a test database and table:</description></item><item><title>Transfer</title><link>/user-guide/aws/transfer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/transfer/</guid><description>Introduction The AWS Transfer API is a powerful tool that empowers users to establish FTP(S) servers with ease. These servers serve as gateways, allowing direct access to files residing in Amazon S3 buckets. This functionality streamlines file management processes, making it simpler and more efficient to handle data stored in S3 by providing a familiar FTP interface for users to interact with their files securely. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to facilitate file transfers or enhance your data access capabilities, the AWS Transfer API simplifies the process and extends the versatility of your cloud storage infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Verified Permissions</title><link>/user-guide/aws/verifiedpermissions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/verifiedpermissions/</guid><description>Introduction Amazon Verified Permissions is a scalable service for managing fine-grained permissions and authorization in custom applications.
It helps secure applications by moving authorization logic outside the app and managing policies in one place, using the Cedar policy language to define access rules.
It checks if a principal can take an action on a resource in a specific context in your application.
LocalStack allows you to use the Verified Permissions APIs in your local environment to test your authorization logic, with integrations with other AWS services like Cognito.</description></item><item><title>Web Application Firewall (WAF)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/waf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/waf/</guid><description>Introduction Web Application Firewall (WAF) is a service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that helps protect your web applications from common web exploits that could affect application availability, compromise security, or consume excessive resources. WAFv2 is the latest version of WAF, and it allows you to specify a single set of rules to protect your web applications, APIs, and mobile applications from common attack patterns, such as SQL injection and cross-site scripting.</description></item><item><title>X-Ray</title><link>/user-guide/aws/xray/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/xray/</guid><description>Introduction X-Ray is a distributed tracing service that helps to understand cross-service interactions and facilitates debugging of performance bottlenecks. Instrumented applications generate trace data by recording trace segments with information about the work tasks of an application, such as timestamps, tasks names, or metadata. X-Ray supports different ways of instrumenting your application including the AWS X-Ray SDK and the AWS Distro for OpenTelemetry (ADOT). X-Ray daemon is an application that gathers raw trace segment data from the X-Ray SDK and relays it to the AWS X-Ray API.</description></item></channel></rss>