<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Supported With Limitations on Docs</title><link>/persistence/supported-with-limitations/</link><description>Recent content in Supported With Limitations on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/persistence/supported-with-limitations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/ec2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/ec2/</guid><description>Introduction Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) is a core service within Amazon Web Services (AWS) that provides scalable and flexible virtual computing resources. EC2 enables users to launch and manage virtual machines, referred to as instances.
LocalStack allows you to use the EC2 APIs in your local environment to create and manage EC2 instances and related resources such as VPCs, EBS volumes, etc. The list of supported APIs can be found on the API coverage page.</description></item><item><title>Lambda</title><link>/user-guide/aws/lambda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/lambda/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Lambda is a Serverless Function as a Service (FaaS) platform that lets you run code in your preferred programming language on the AWS ecosystem. AWS Lambda automatically scales your code to meet demand and handles server provisioning, management, and maintenance. AWS Lambda allows you to break down your application into smaller, independent functions that integrate seamlessly with AWS services.
LocalStack allows you to use the Lambda APIs to create, deploy, and test your Lambda functions.</description></item><item><title>Managed Streaming for Kafka (MSK)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/msk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/msk/</guid><description>Introduction Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka (MSK) is a fully managed Apache Kafka service that allows you to build and run applications that process streaming data. MSK offers a centralized platform to facilitate seamless communication between various AWS services and applications through event-driven architectures, facilitating data ingestion, processing, and analytics for various applications. MSK also features automatic scaling and built-in monitoring, allowing users to build robust, high-throughput data pipelines.
LocalStack allows you to use the MSK APIs in your local environment to spin up Kafka clusters on the local machine, create topics for exchanging messages, and define event source mappings that trigger Lambda functions when messages are received on a certain topic.</description></item><item><title>Relational Database Service (RDS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/rds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/rds/</guid><description>Introduction Relational Database Service (RDS) is a managed database service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that allows users to setup, operate, and scale relational databases in the cloud. RDS allows you to deploy and manage various relational database engines like MySQL, PostgreSQL, MariaDB, and Microsoft SQL Server. RDS handles routine database tasks such as provisioning, patching, backup, recovery, and scaling.
LocalStack allows you to use the RDS APIs in your local environment to create and manage RDS clusters and instances for testing &amp;amp; integration purposes.</description></item></channel></rss>