<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pro Image on Docs</title><link>/tags/pro-image/</link><description>Recent content in Pro Image on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/pro-image/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CodeBuild</title><link>/user-guide/aws/codebuild/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/codebuild/</guid><description>Introduction AWS CodeBuild is a fully managed continuous integration service that compiles source code, runs tests, and produces software packages that are ready to deploy. It is part of the AWS Developer Tools suite and integrates with other AWS services to provide an end-to-end development pipeline.
LocalStack supports the emulation of most of the CodeBuild operations. The supported operations are listed on the API coverage page.
AWS CodeBuild emulation is powered by the AWS CodeBuild agent.</description></item><item><title>CodeDeploy</title><link>/user-guide/aws/codedeploy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/codedeploy/</guid><description>Introduction CodeDeploy is a service that automates application deployments. On AWS, it supports deployments to Amazon EC2 instances, on-premises instances, serverless Lambda functions, or Amazon ECS services. Furthermore, based on the target it is also possible to use an in-place deployment or a blue/green deployment.
LocalStack supports a mocking of CodeDeploy API operations. The supported operations are listed on the API coverage page.
Getting Started This guide will walk through the process of creating CodeDeploy applications, deployment configuration, deployment groups, and deployments.</description></item><item><title>CodePipeline</title><link>/user-guide/aws/codepipeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/codepipeline/</guid><description>Introduction CodePipeline is a continuous integration/continuous delivery (CI/CD) service offered by AWS. CodePipeline can be used to create automated pipelines that handle the build, test and deployment of software.
LocalStack comes with a bespoke execution engine that can be used to create, manage, and execute pipelines. It supports a variety of actions that integrate with S3, CodeBuild, CodeConnections, and more. The available operations can be found on the API coverage page.</description></item></channel></rss>