<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise Plan on Docs</title><link>/tags/enterprise-plan/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise Plan on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/enterprise-plan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Outages Extension</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/outages-extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/outages-extension/</guid><description>Introduction The LocalStack Outages Extension allows you to mimic outages across any AWS region or service. By integrating the Outages Extension using the LocalStack Extension mechanism, you can assess your infrastructure&amp;rsquo;s robustness. Intentionally triggering service outages and monitoring the system&amp;rsquo;s response in situations where the infrastructure is compromised offers a powerful way to test. This strategy helps gauge the effectiveness of the system&amp;rsquo;s deployment procedures and its resilience against infrastructure disruptions, which is a key element of chaos engineering.</description></item><item><title>Special Configurations</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/special-configs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/special-configs/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack allows users to inject intentional errors, particularly in Kinesis and DynamoDB. You can introduce controlled chaos into your development environment enhance to enhance service resilience. By configuring environment variables, you can simulate disruptions. This simple setup helps improve the response mechanisms of these key AWS services, ensuring robust architecture under challenging conditions with minimal initial configuration.
This guide demonstrates the DYNAMODB_ERROR_PROBABILITY and KINESIS_ERROR_PROBABILITY configuration flags. The guide assumes basic knowledge of the AWS CLI and our awslocal wrapper script.</description></item><item><title>SSO for Azure AD</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/single-sign-on/azure-ad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/single-sign-on/azure-ad/</guid><description>To configure SSO with an Azure AD Enterprise application, we provide a simple step-by-step solution below:
Navigate to &amp;ldquo;Set up single sign on&amp;rdquo; in your Azure AD Enterprise application.
In the Basic SAML Configuration, ensure that the settings match the following details
Take the correct values for Identifier (Entity ID) and Reply URL from the Identity Provider configuration page.
In the Attributes &amp;amp; Claims section, add a group claim with the following configuration and save it.</description></item><item><title>CI Analytics</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/ci-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/ci-analytics/</guid><description>Introduction CI Analytics is a feature of LocalStack Web Application that allows users to get insights into their CI builds. CI Analytics unifies additional features, such as Cloud Pods &amp;amp; Stack Insights, and augments them with an integrated view of CI builds to provide users with insights and facilitate debugging. The features include:
CI Project Runs: Offers a unified view of all CI builds for a particular project. Log Output: Enables viewing of detailed logs for individual CI builds.</description></item><item><title>Single-Sign On</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/single-sign-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/single-sign-on/</guid><description>Custom Single-Sign On (SSO) Identity providers, can be enabled to facilitate the process of quickly onboarding team members from your organization.
In order to configure SSO access, first sign in to the LocalStack Web application under app.localstack.cloud. In your profile settings, navigate to the Single Sign-on tab which will list existing SSO Identity Providers (if any exist).
Next, click the button to create a new identity provider (IdP), where you can choose between the two leading industry standards:</description></item><item><title>Database Migration Service (DMS)</title><link>/user-guide/aws/dms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/aws/dms/</guid><description>Introduction AWS Database Migration Service provides migration solution from databases, data warehouses, and other type of data stores (e.g. S3, SAP). The migration can be homogeneous (source and target have the same type), but often times is heterogeneous as it supports migration from various sources to various targets (self-hosted and AWS services).
LocalStack only supports selected use cases for DMS at the moment. The supported APIs are available on our API coverage page, which provides information on the extent of DMS integration with LocalStack.</description></item></channel></rss>