<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LocalStack Enterprise on Docs</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack Enterprise on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enterprise Image</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-image/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack offers an Enterprise image that allows offline usage and includes a customer-specific configuration. This offline functionality is enabled by:
Pre-installed packages required for running specific services that are usually downloaded on demand (such as opensearch or dynamodb-local). A certificate keypair for localhost.localstack.cloud to resolve to the LocalStack container via our DNS server. An embedded decryption key in the image, eliminating the need to contact the license server to operate LocalStack.</description></item><item><title>K8s Operator</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/k8s-operator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/k8s-operator/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack K8s operator is a custom Kubernetes operator that offers LocalStack emulator as a native resource in Kubernetes environments. The operator is designed to simplify the deployment and management of LocalStack in Kubernetes clusters.
Installation To install the K8s operator, run the following commands:
$ kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/localstack/localstack-k8s-operator/v0.2.0/release/crds.yaml $ kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/localstack/localstack-k8s-operator/v0.2.0/release/controller.yaml You can then deploy a LocalStack instance by storing the following file content as localstack.yml and applying it against the cluster via kubectl apply -f localstack.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Support</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/enterprise-support/</guid><description>Introduction A customer portal is a home behind a login where customers can view, open, and reply to their support tickets. Currently, the customer portal is only available to Enterprise customers.
You can find the customer portal here: https://support.localstack.cloud/portal
Signing up for Enterprise Support If you are a member of an organization with an enterprise LocalStack subscription, you will receive an invitation to create an account and join the LocalStack Support Portal via email.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Executor</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/kubernetes-executor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/kubernetes-executor/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Enterprise provides a Kubernetes executor for compute services like EC2, ECS, and Lambda. It allows you to run EC2 instances, ECS tasks, and Lambda functions in your Kubernetes clusters. By default, LocalStack uses the docker backend for compute services. You can switch to the kubernetes executor by setting the appropriate environment variables.
EC2 Kubernetes Executor The LocalStack Enterprise image allows you to run EC2 instances on Kubernetes. You can do so by setting the EC2_VM_MANAGER environment variable to kubernetes in the LocalStack container.</description></item><item><title>CI Analytics</title><link>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/ci-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/localstack-enterprise/ci-analytics/</guid><description>Introduction CI Analytics is a feature of LocalStack Web Application that allows users to get insights into their CI builds. CI Analytics unifies additional features, such as Cloud Pods &amp;amp; Stack Insights, and augments them with an integrated view of CI builds to provide users with insights and facilitate debugging. The features include:
CI Project Runs: Offers a unified view of all CI builds for a particular project. Log Output: Enables viewing of detailed logs for individual CI builds.</description></item></channel></rss>