<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CloudFormation on Docs</title><link>/tags/cloudformation/</link><description>Recent content in CloudFormation on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/cloudformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building a Java Notification app using AWS Java SDK, Simple Email Service (SES), and CloudFormation</title><link>/tutorials/java-notification-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/java-notification-app/</guid><description>Java is a popular platform for cloud applications that use Amazon Web Services. With the AWS Java SDK, Java developers can build applications that work with various AWS services, like Simple Email Service (SES), Simple Queue Service (SQS), Simple Notification Service (SNS), and more. Simple Email Service (SES) is a cloud-based email-sending service that enables developers to integrate email functionality into their applications running on AWS. SES allows developers to work without an on-prem Simple Mail Transfer Protocol (SMTP) system and send bulk emails to many recipients.</description></item><item><title>Deploying containers on Elastic Container Service (ECS) clusters using Elastic Container Registry (ECR) and AWS Fargate, with LocalStack</title><link>/tutorials/ecs-ecr-container-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/ecs-ecr-container-app/</guid><description>Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) is a fully-managed container orchestration service that simplifies the deployment, management, and scaling of Docker containers on AWS. With support for two launch types, EC2 and Fargate, ECS allows you to run containers on your cluster of EC2 instances or have AWS manage your underlying infrastructure with Fargate. The Fargate launch type provides a serverless-like experience for running containers, allowing you to focus on your applications instead of infrastructure.</description></item></channel></rss>