<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chaos Engineering on Docs</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/</link><description>Recent content in Chaos Engineering on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/user-guide/chaos-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS Fault Injection Service</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/fault-injection-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/fault-injection-service/</guid><description>Introduction The Fault Injection Service is a fully managed service by AWS designed to help you improve the resilience of your applications by simulating real-world outages and operational issues. This service allows you to conduct controlled experiments on your AWS infrastructure, injecting faults and observing how your system responds under various conditions.
By using the Fault Injection Service, you can identify weaknesses, test recovery procedures, and ensure that your applications can withstand unexpected disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Chaos API</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-api/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Chaos API allows you to mimic outages across any AWS region or service. Intentionally triggering service outages and monitoring the system&amp;rsquo;s response in situations where the infrastructure is compromised offers a powerful way to test. This strategy helps gauge the effectiveness of the system&amp;rsquo;s deployment procedures and its resilience against infrastructure disruptions, which is a key element of chaos engineering.
You can use LocalStack Chaos API to cause API failures for any combination of the following:</description></item><item><title>Chaos Engineering Dashboard</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-application-dashboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/chaos-application-dashboard/</guid><description>Introduction The Chaos Engineering Dashboard in LocalStack offers streamlined testing for cloud applications, enabling you to simulate server errors, service outages, regional disruptions, and network latency with ease, ensuring your app is ready for real-world challenges.
The dashboard uses LocalStack Chaos API under the hood to offer a set of customizable templates that can be seamlessly integrated into any automation workflows.
You can find this feature in the LocalStack Web Application by navigating to app.</description></item><item><title>Outages Extension</title><link>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/outages-extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/chaos-engineering/outages-extension/</guid><description>Introduction Warning Outages Extension has been deprecated. It is recommended to migrate to the Chaos API. The LocalStack Outages Extension allows you to mimic outages across any AWS region or service. By integrating the Outages Extension using the LocalStack Extension mechanism, you can assess your infrastructure&amp;rsquo;s robustness. Intentionally triggering service outages and monitoring the system&amp;rsquo;s response in situations where the infrastructure is compromised offers a powerful way to test. This strategy helps gauge the effectiveness of the system&amp;rsquo;s deployment procedures and its resilience against infrastructure disruptions, which is a key element of chaos engineering.</description></item></channel></rss>