<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LocalStack Web Application on Docs</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack Web Application on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/user-guide/web-application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accounts</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/accounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/accounts/</guid><description>Introduction A user account on the LocalStack Web Application is required to access the following features:
Advanced AWS services Resource Browsers Cloud Pods Extensions Library Stack Insights Ephemeral Instances IAM Policy Stream Chaos Engineering To create an Auth Token for your LocalStack account, you need to sign up for an account on the LocalStack Web Application.
This token is used to authenticate your requests to the LocalStack platform and access the features mentioned above.</description></item><item><title>Workspace</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/workspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/workspace/</guid><description>Introduction In LocalStack, a Workspace is the foundational unit for organizing users, resources, and billing.
It enables collaboration across teams and provides access to shared capabilities.
Workspace Features These include:
Cloud Pods : Manage and share your state snapshots. Stack Insights: Monitor and observe your LocalStack usage. Extensions: Access the Extensions Library. You can find these under the Workspace section in the left sidebar.
Workspace Settings Workspace settings can be accessed by clicking your or your organization&amp;rsquo;s name in the top-left corner → Settings → Workspace.</description></item><item><title>Users and Licenses</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/users-and-licenses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/users-and-licenses/</guid><description>Introduction The Users &amp;amp; Licenses page in the LocalStack Web Application allows workspace administrators to manage user memberships, assign licenses, and transition users from legacy API keys to the new license system.
To access this page:
Click on your name in the top-left corner of the dashboard. Go to Settings → Users &amp;amp; Licenses under the Administration section. Managing Users Inviting Users To invite someone to your workspace:
Go to the Invite User section.</description></item><item><title>Resource Browser</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/resource-browser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/resource-browser/</guid><description>Introduction The LocalStack Resource Browser allow you to view, manage, and deploy AWS resources locally while building &amp;amp; testing their cloud applications locally. It provides an internal, integrated experience, similar to the AWS Management Console, to manage the ephemeral resources in a LocalStack container on your local machine.
The Resource Browser provide an experience similar to the AWS Management Console. However, the Resource Browser is not a replacement for the AWS Management Console and only replicate some of the features of the AWS Management Console.</description></item><item><title>Instance Management</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/instance-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/instance-management/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Instance Management lets you view and manage your LocalStack instances while you build and test your cloud applications locally. You can access this feature through the LocalStack Instances section in the sidebar of the LocalStack Web Application.
Instance Management offers these features:
Overview: Shows the stack details of your LocalStack instances. Status: Shows the status of the services running in the LocalStack container. Resource Browser: Lets you view and manage your local AWS resources.</description></item><item><title>Stack Insights</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/stack-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/stack-insights/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack collects execution events to provide usage analytics and insights into development and testing. Stack Insights let users report AWS API usage telemetry to their LocalStack account.
Stack Insights show which APIs are used, which clients or integrations use specific services and API operations, and which services cause the most API errors.
Note Your privacy matters to us! We only collect anonymized and sanitized data. No sensitive information about your application is ever collected or exposed.</description></item><item><title>Stack Overview</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/stack-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/stack-overview/</guid><description>Introduction The Stack Overview provides a summary of deployed resources, categorized services with configurations, and quick access to resource details like identifiers and endpoints.
You can access the Stack Overview in the LocalStack Web Application. Alternatively, go to your LocalStack Instance and click on Overview to see a high-level visualization of your locally running cloud app architecture.
Note Stack Overview is offered as a preview feature and is under active development.</description></item><item><title>CI Keys (Deprecated)</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/ci-keys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/ci-keys/</guid><description>Warning LocalStack CI Keys are now deprecated, and the option to issue or retrieve a CI Key has been removed from the LocalStack Web Application. Users are advised to switch to CI Auth Tokens, which are designed for use in CI environments and other non-developer contexts. CI Auth Tokens can be managed on the Auth Tokens page.
To migrate to CI Auth Tokens, follow these steps:
Retrieve your CI Auth Token from the Auth Tokens page.</description></item></channel></rss>