<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LocalStack Web Application on Docs</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack Web Application on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/user-guide/web-application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accounts</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/accounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/accounts/</guid><description>A LocalStack account is required to access features in the web app, and to access any of our paid offerings.
Creating an Account Visit app.localstack.cloud/sign-up to create a user account for LocalStack. You can sign up with your email address or one of our supported social identity providers (such as GitHub).
The Terms and Conditions can be found at https://www.localstack.cloud/legal/tos and our privacy policy can be found at https://www.localstack.cloud/legal/privacy-policy
Updating Account Info and Settings To update your account info, password and settings select the corresponding entry from the sidebar under the &amp;lsquo;Account&amp;rsquo; menu entry.</description></item><item><title>Workspaces</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/workspaces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/workspaces/</guid><description>In LocalStack, a workspace allows you to collaborate with members of your organization and it encapsulates user and license management, subscriptions and billing, as well as access to shared resources and features like Cloud Pods or Stack Insights.
A workspace represents the base organizational unit in the web application. Users can be invited to join a workspace, and an admin can manage their license and permissions inside a workspace.</description></item><item><title>Managing Users and Licenses</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/users-licences/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/users-licences/</guid><description>Within a workspace, users and their associated licenses are managed on the Users &amp;amp; Licenses page. This page allows to manage users and assign licenses to them.
Managing Users Inviting Users to the Workspace New and existing LocalStack users can be invited to a workspace in the &amp;lsquo;Invite Users&amp;rsquo; section. To invite a user, provide the user&amp;rsquo;s name and email address. If the invitee does not have a LocalStack account yet, an invitation to create an account will be sent to the provided email address.</description></item><item><title>Resource Browser</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/resource-browser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/resource-browser/</guid><description>Introduction The LocalStack Resource Browser allow you to view, manage, and deploy AWS resources locally while building &amp;amp; testing their cloud applications locally. It provides an internal, integrated experience, similar to the AWS Management Console, to manage the ephemeral resources in a LocalStack container on your local machine.
The Resource Browser provide an experience similar to the AWS Management Console. However, the Resource Browser is not a replacement for the AWS Management Console and only replicate some of the features of the AWS Management Console.</description></item><item><title>Instance Management</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/instance-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/instance-management/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Instance Management lets you view and manage your LocalStack instances while you build and test your cloud applications locally. You can access this feature through the LocalStack Instances section in the sidebar of the LocalStack Web Application.
Instance Management offers these features:
Status: Shows the status of the services running in the LocalStack container. Resource Browser: Lets you view and manage your local AWS resources. State: Allows you to export and import the state of your LocalStack instances.</description></item><item><title>Stack Insights</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/stack-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/stack-insights/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack collects execution events to provide usage analytics and insights into development and testing. Stack Insights let users report AWS API usage telemetry to their LocalStack account.
Stack Insights show which APIs are used, which clients or integrations use specific services and API operations, and which services cause the most API errors.
Note Your privacy matters to us! We only collect anonymized and sanitized data. No sensitive information about your application is ever collected or exposed.</description></item><item><title>Stack Overview</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/stack-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/stack-overview/</guid><description>Introduction The Stack Overview provides a summary of deployed resources, categorized services with configurations, and quick access to resource details like identifiers and endpoints.
You can access the Stack Overview in the LocalStack Web Application. Alternatively, go to your LocalStack Instance and click on Overview to see a high-level visualization of your locally running cloud app architecture.
Supported Resources The following resources are supported by Stack Overview:
AWS::ApiGateway::RestApi AWS::CloudFormation::Stack AWS::DynamoDB::Table AWS::EC2::VPC AWS::Events::EventBus AWS::IAM::Group AWS::IAM::Role AWS::IAM::User AWS::Lambda::Function AWS::S3::Bucket AWS::SES::EmailIdentity AWS::SNS::Topic AWS::SQS::Queue AWS::SSM::Parameter AWS::SecretsManager::Secret AWS::StepFunctions::StateMachine AWS::CloudFront::Distribution AWS::Pipes::Pipe</description></item><item><title>CI Keys (Deprecated)</title><link>/user-guide/web-application/ci-keys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guide/web-application/ci-keys/</guid><description>Warning LocalStack CI Keys are now deprecated, and the option to issue or retrieve a CI Key has been removed from the LocalStack Web Application. Users are advised to switch to CI Auth Tokens, which are designed for use in CI environments and other non-developer contexts. CI Auth Tokens can be managed on the Auth Tokens page.
To migrate to CI Auth Tokens, follow these steps:
Retrieve your CI Auth Token from the Auth Tokens page.</description></item></channel></rss>