<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API Gateway on Docs</title><link>/tags/api-gateway/</link><description>Recent content in API Gateway on Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/api-gateway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How To: Collaborative AWS local development with LocalStack’s Cloud Pods</title><link>/tutorials/cloud-pods-collaborative-debugging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/cloud-pods-collaborative-debugging/</guid><description>Introduction By replicating environments, teams can share the exact conditions under which a bug occurs.
For developing AWS applications locally, the tool of choice is LocalStack, which can sustain a full-blown comprehensive stack. However, when issues appear, and engineers need a second opinion from a colleague, recreating the environment from scratch can leave details slipping through the cracks. This is where Cloud Pods come in, to encapsulate the state of the LocalStack instance and allow for seamless collaboration.</description></item><item><title>Chaos Engineering: Route53 Failover</title><link>/tutorials/route-53-failover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/route-53-failover/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack allows you to integrate and test Chaos API with Route53 to automatically divert users to a healthy secondary zone if the primary region fails, ensuring system availability and responsiveness. Route53&amp;rsquo;s health checks and traffic redirection enhance architecture resilience and ensure service continuity during regional outages, crucial for uninterrupted user experiences.
Note Route53 Failover and Chaos API is currently available as part of the LocalStack Enterprise plan. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to try it out, please contact us to request access.</description></item><item><title>Chaos Engineering: Simulating Outages using Chaos API</title><link>/tutorials/simulating-outages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tutorials/simulating-outages/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Chaos API is capable of simulating infrastructure faults to allow conducting controlled chaos engineering tests on AWS infrastructure. Its purpose is to uncover vulnerabilities and improve system robustness. Chaos API offers a means to deliberately introduce failures and observe their impacts, helping developers to better equip their systems against actual outages.
Getting started In this tutorial we study the effects of outages on a sample AWS application. We use the Chaos API to simulate the outage and design a mitigation to make the application resilient against database outages.</description></item></channel></rss>